Update 2.0
Major changes:
Removed a separate tab for days of the week and additional settings
All settings are combined in one "Alarm Settings" tab
The interface is divided into two columns:
Left: basic parameters (time, message, sound)
Right: days of the week and additional settings
Added grouping frames for better visual organization
Simplified navigation - now all settings are available on one tab at once.

Major improvements:

Error handling:
Added try-except blocks for all critical operations
Improved time validation
Checking the size of audio files
Audio playback error handling

Additional settings:
Added the "Additional Settings" tab
The ability to set default settings
Setting the number of repetitions of the signal
Setting the snooze time

New features:
Postponing the alarm (the "Postpone" button)
MP3 file support via the pygame library
Checking for duplicates when adding an alarm clock
Sorting alarms by time in the list

Interface improvements:
More informative display of alarms in the list
Increased window size
Detailed error messages

Stability:
Protection against failures when saving/loading settings
Handling critical errors in the main loop


Update 1.0
Added a list for storing multiple alarms
Added a new "My Alarms" tab to display all alarms.
The following functions are implemented:
add_alarm() - adding a new alarm clock
stop_all_alarms() - stop all alarms
stop_selected_alarm() - stop selected alarm
remove_alarm() - delete alarm
update_alarms_list() - updating the alarm list
The logic of checking alarm triggers in update_time()
has been changed. Saving the status of each alarm (active/inactive) has been added
. The display of alarm information in the list has been improved.

Now the user can:
Add an unlimited number of alarms
Manage each alarm separately (stop/delete)
See a list of all alarms with their statuses
Set different settings for each alarm (time, sound, message, days of the week)
Alarms are saved between program starts and run until they are stopped by the user.